{"sentences": [", meaning \" Western District \" , is a common ward name in many Japanese cities .\n", "Nishi - ku , Fukuoka , in Fukuoka , Fukuoka Prefecture \n"], "toktext": [[[",", ","], ["meaning", "mean"], ["\"", "\""], ["Western", "Western"], ["District", "District"], ["\"", "\""], [",", ","], ["is", "be"], ["a", "a"], ["common", "common"], ["ward", "ward"], ["name", "name"], ["in", "in"], ["many", "many"], ["Japanese", "Japanese"], ["cities", "city"], [".", "."]], [["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Fukuoka", "Fukuoka"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Fukuoka", "Fukuoka"], [",", ","], ["Fukuoka", "Fukuoka"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Hamamatsu", "Hamamatsu"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Hamamatsu", "Hamamatsu"], [",", ","], ["Shizuoka", "Shizuoka"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Hiroshima", "Hiroshima"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Hiroshima", "Hiroshima"], [",", ","], ["Hiroshima", "Hiroshima"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Kōbe", "Kōbe"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Kobe", "Kobe"], [",", ","], ["Hyōgo", "Hyōgo"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Kumamoto", "Kumamoto"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Kumamoto", "Kumamoto"], [",", ","], ["Kumamoto", "Kumamoto"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Nagoya", "Nagoya"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Nagoya", "Nagoya"], [",", ","], ["Aichi", "Aichi"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Niigata", "Niigata"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Niigata", "Niigata"], [",", ","], ["Niigata", "Niigata"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Ōsaka", "Ōsaka"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Osaka", "Osaka"], [",", ","], ["Osaka", "Osaka"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Saitama", "Saitama"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Saitama", "Saitama"], [",", ","], ["Saitama", "Saitama"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Sakai", "Sakai"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Sakai", "Sakai"], [",", ","], ["Osaka", "Osaka"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Sapporo", "Sapporo"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Sapporo", "Sapporo"], [",", ","], ["Hokkaido", "Hokkaido"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"], ["Nishi", "Nishi"], ["-", "-"], ["ku", "ku"], [",", ","], ["Yokohama", "Yokohama"], [",", ","], ["in", "in"], ["Yokohama", "Yokohama"], [",", ","], ["Kanagawa", "Kanagawa"], ["Prefecture", "Prefecture"]]], "constit": ["(ROOT\n  (S\n    (S (, ,)\n      (VP (VBG meaning)\n        (NP (`` \") (NNP Western) (NNP District) ('' \")))\n      (, ,))\n    (VP (VBZ is)\n      (NP\n        (NP (DT a) (JJ common) (NN ward) (NN name))\n        (PP (IN in)\n          (NP (JJ many) (JJ Japanese) (NNS cities)))))\n    (. .)))\n", "(ROOT\n  (NP\n    (NP (NNP Nishi))\n    (HYPH -)\n    (NP\n      (NP\n        (NML\n          (NML (NNP ku))\n          (, ,)\n          (NP (NNP Fukuoka))\n          (, ,)))\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Fukuoka)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Fukuoka) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Hamamatsu))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Hamamatsu)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Shizuoka) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Hiroshima))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Hiroshima)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Hiroshima) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Kōbe))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Kobe)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Hyōgo) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Kumamoto))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Kumamoto)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Kumamoto) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Nagoya))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Nagoya)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Aichi) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Niigata))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Niigata)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Niigata) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Ōsaka))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Osaka)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Osaka) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Saitama))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Saitama)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Saitama) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Sakai))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Sakai)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Osaka) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Sapporo))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Sapporo)))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Hokkaido) (NNP Prefecture) (NNP Nishi) (HYPH -) (NNP ku))\n      (, ,)\n      (NP (NNP Yokohama))\n      (, ,)\n      (PP (IN in)\n        (NP (NNP Yokohama) (, ,) (NNP Kanagawa) (NNP Prefecture))))))\n"], "coref": [[[1, 103, 103], [1, 106, 106]], [[1, 48, 48], [1, 51, 51]], [[1, 86, 90], [1, 108, 112]], [[1, 114, 114], [1, 117, 117]], [[1, 59, 59], [1, 62, 62]], [[1, 4, 4], [1, 7, 7]], [[1, 70, 70], [1, 73, 73]], [[1, 26, 26], [1, 29, 29]]], "srl": [{"arguments": [[[1, 1, "V"], [2, 5, "N-ARG-A1"]], [[7, 7, "V"], [1, 5, "N-ARG-A1"], [8, 11, "N-ARG-A2"], [12, 15, "N-ARGM-LOC"]]], "frameset_ids": ["01", "01"], "lemmas": ["mean", "be"], "plabel": [["ARG0", "ARG1", "TMP"], ["ARG1", "ARG2", "MNR", "ADV", "LOC", "PRD", "DIS"]], "plemma_ids": ["mean.01", "be.01"], "predicates": [1, 7], "sentence": [",", "meaning", "'", "Western", "District", "'", ",", "is", "a", "common", "ward", "name", "in", "many", "Japanese", "cities", "."]}, {"arguments": [], "frameset_ids": [], "lemmas": [], "plabel": [], "plemma_ids": [], "predicates": [], "sentence": ["Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Fukuoka", ",", "in", "Fukuoka", ",", "Fukuoka", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Hamamatsu", ",", "in", "Hamamatsu", ",", "Shizuoka", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Hiroshima", ",", "in", "Hiroshima", ",", "Hiroshima", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Kōbe", ",", "in", "Kobe", ",", "Hyōgo", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Kumamoto", ",", "in", "Kumamoto", ",", "Kumamoto", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Nagoya", ",", "in", "Nagoya", ",", "Aichi", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Niigata", ",", "in", "Niigata", ",", "Niigata", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Ōsaka", ",", "in", "Osaka", ",", "Osaka", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Saitama", ",", "in", "Saitama", ",", "Saitama", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Sakai", ",", "in", "Sakai", ",", "Osaka", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Sapporo", ",", "in", "Sapporo", ",", "Hokkaido", "Prefecture", "Nishi", "-", "ku", ",", "Yokohama", ",", "in", "Yokohama", ",", "Kanagawa", "Prefecture"]}], "wsd": [[0, 1, "mean%2:32:03::"], [0, 7, "be%2:42:06::"], [0, 9, "common%5:00:00:familiar:02"], [0, 10, "ward%1:15:00::"], [0, 11, "name%1:10:00::"], [0, 13, "many%3:00:00::"], [0, 15, "city%1:15:00::"]], "entities": [[0, 3, 4, "MISC"], [0, 14, 14, "NATIONALITY"], [1, 0, 2, "PERSON"], [1, 4, 4, "LOCATION"], [1, 7, 7, "LOCATION"], [1, 9, 13, "LOCATION"], [1, 15, 15, "ORGANIZATION"], [1, 18, 18, "CITY"], [1, 20, 24, "LOCATION"], [1, 26, 26, "CITY"], [1, 29, 29, "CITY"], [1, 31, 31, "CITY"], [1, 32, 35, "LOCATION"], [1, 37, 37, "PERSON"], [1, 40, 40, "CITY"], [1, 42, 46, "LOCATION"], [1, 48, 48, "LOCATION"], [1, 51, 51, "LOCATION"], [1, 53, 57, "LOCATION"], [1, 59, 59, "CITY"], [1, 62, 62, "CITY"], [1, 64, 68, "LOCATION"], [1, 70, 70, "CITY"], [1, 73, 73, "CITY"], [1, 75, 75, "CITY"], [1, 76, 79, "LOCATION"], [1, 81, 81, "LOCATION"], [1, 84, 84, "LOCATION"], [1, 86, 90, "LOCATION"], [1, 92, 92, "CITY"], [1, 95, 95, "CITY"], [1, 97, 97, "CITY"], [1, 98, 101, "LOCATION"], [1, 103, 103, "CITY"], [1, 106, 106, "CITY"], [1, 108, 112, "LOCATION"], [1, 114, 114, "LOCATION"], [1, 117, 117, "LOCATION"], [1, 121, 123, "PERSON"], [1, 125, 125, "LOCATION"], [1, 128, 128, "LOCATION"]]}